Prophecy Time
Come on, come here!
You pose as a pastor. Are you really a pastor?
Yes, sir!
Because I'm seeing you acting and doing the work of a pastor.
Are you a pastor?
Yes, sir!
But if you are a pastor, what is your business with rituals?
I needed money.
You went there to do what?
To take money.
He is my husband, Man of God, please deliver him!
Man of God, please deliver him.
He is a pastor.
He used to do the work of God.
Come out.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Testimony Time
My name is Pastor Stephen Zoryiku.
I'm a first year marketing student at Accra Polytechnic.
This is my wife Evelyn and we are from Ghana.
On Monday, the prophet gave me a prophecy that he saw me as a pastor
and I said "yes" and he asked what my connection was with rituals.
I confirmed that to be true because
because after my Bible school I started preaching the Word of God to people
and praying for them as well.
One evening whilst I was passing, I met this guy on the floor
with people gathered around him.
The man said that he was seeing some short demons piercing his chest with spears.
He said he was dying.
I felt moved by the power of God to pray for him.
I went home, took some anointing oil, went back and started praying.
As soon as I started, this man got up and started beating me.
The following day, I did not feel okay.
I began to feel like taking ritual money.
It continued and then, one of my friends took me to a ritualist to take ritual money.
They demanded for five human fingers and an embryo
which I was not able to provide.
So I left and then relocated to another town with my wife.
Everything began to fall apart, including my business.
I had a very strong feeling that I needed to take that money
in order to be free at once and for all.
I started moving around, looking for where I could get it.
When I came here with my wife to Nigeria,
the feeling became so strong and I decided that this was the time to take it.
So I looked around for somewhere I could take money.
I went there with the mind that whatever they demanded from me,
I would be ready to give.
So I went to a ritualist and told him about my situation, that I wanted money
and he said that before he could start anything, I needed to bring N10,000.
I didn't have the money so I told him I would be back.
I got home and then came together with my wife to church,
and received the prophecy from the man of God.
After the prophecy, the thought of taking ritual money is gone.
Before, I would dream of short demons chasing me with axes
and I would see people coming to steal my money and many other dreams.
Now, I no longer have such dreams.
So I give thanks to God for delivering me.
Testimony Time
There is trouble all over the world.
Even the trouble in the House of God is so much.
Who is a pastor now? Who is a prophet, all over the world?
That is the trouble now.
There is trouble, so we need to pray for the church.
Please rise up, let's pray for the church.
Pray for the church. Ask God to redeem the church.
Redeem the assembly.
Ask God to purge the church.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ we pray.
Ask God to purge the church, overhaul the church.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Remember your pastor in prayer.
Ask God to guide your pastor.
If your pastor needs to be purged, ask God to purge him.
Purge him, sanctify him.
Make real church.
Let the Church of the Acts of the Apostles come down in our day.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Brother, you have seen everything that happened. So we thank God.
If I were you now, the Word "I'm a pastor" you still lay a claim on,
why can't you just let us pray and ask God, "What is your direction".
Okay, I think this is what we're going to do now.
So thank you.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date for the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing The World
TT: Lizz ndungu 10/7/2017
RV: Jacqueline 07/01/18 + Mel